<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>inProd Latest News</title>
		<link>http://inprod.co/news</link>
		<description>The latest news from Inverted Productions</description>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 10:21:00 EST</pubDate>
		<copyright>Inverted Productions</copyright>
		<item>
			<title>Happy Holidays!</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post16</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					Happy Winter Solstice!  As you might have seen on the inProd social media feeds, a new game is being delivered for the holidays!  <a href="/games/workshopscramble" style="font-size: italic;">Workshop Scramble</a> has you helping the elves in Santa's workshop assemble toys for the good kids of the world.  It's a fast-paced arcade-y, puzzle-y mobile game, and you can grab it <strong>right now</strong> on the <a href="https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=co.inprod.WorkshopScramble" target="_blank">Google Play Store</a> or <a href="https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/p/workshop-scramble/9pp0953tfssm" target="_blank">Microsoft Store</a>!
				</p>
				<p>
					Officially, this is an early-access open beta, but stay tuned for the official release on Christmas, with a few features that aren't ready for prime time just yet.  If you want to keep up with the latest news on this particular game, you can follow <i>Workshop Scramble</i> on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Workshop-Scramble-308846489966788" target="_blank">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/WorkshopScramble" target="_blank">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://twitter.com/WorkshopScrambl" target="_blank">Twitter</a>!
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 10:21:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>*Static Crackle*</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post15</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					Hello?  Is this thing still on?
				</p>
				<p>
					It has been quite a while, but inProd is back and better than ever with a new site, new logo, and new games!  Site changes are still going to be rolling out over the next couple weeks, but the bigger news is the annoucement of our new game, <a href="/games/bananasplit"><i>Banana Split</i></a>, a tasty twist of third-person shooting and real-time strategy for sweet multiplayer action!  Follow <i>Banana Split</i> on <a href="https://www.facebook.com/BananaSplitGame" target="_blank">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://plus.google.com/+BananaSplitGame" target="_blank">Google+</a>, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/BananaSplitGame" target="_blank">Instagram</a>, or <a href="https://twitter.com/BananaSplitGame" target="_blank">Twitter</a> for updates as work on the game continues, or if you are in the area, come try it for yourself at <a href="https://www.rocgamefest.com" target="_blank">ROC Game Fest</a> in Rochester, New York on September 30<sup>th</sup>!
				</p>
				<p>
					For general inProd news, our old <a href="https://www.facebook.com/inProdGames" target="_blank">Facebook</a> and <a href="https://plus.google.com/117553032782875379546" target="_blank">Google+</a> feeds are back up and running, along with our new <a href="https://www.instagram.com/inProdGames" target="_blank">Instagram</a> and <a href="https://twitter.com/inProdGames" target="_blank">Twitter</a>, and for those who have been with us since the very beginning, you might remember our very first game, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/LegitTD" target="_blank">Legitimate</a> <a href="https://plus.google.com/116844040350643203041" target="_blank">Tower</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/LegitTD" target="_blank">Defense</a>.
				</p>
				<p>
					That is all for now.  Stay tuned for more in the coming months, but for now, thanks for welcoming us back into your Internet :)
				</p>
				<p style="font-size: small; font-style: italic;">Post was edited to update social media URLs.</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 20:17:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Website Upgrade</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post14</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					For a while now we have had an experimental HTML5/CSS3-based version of our home page available.  Today, we are bringing that to the rest of our site.  In addition, the site has been mostly rebuilt behind-the-scenes.  For those of you who do not speak geek, that means a faster, prettier, and more responsive site.  Game pages have been fixed up, and other parts of the site have been spiced up with little animations.  We hope you enjoy the improved experience as well as other improvements to the site coming over the next month or so.
				</p>
				<p style="font-size:smaller;">
					Note: This update also means we are no longer supporting older versions of Internet Explorer.  If the site looks a bit wonky in your Internet Exploror browser, you will need to download <a href="http://google.com/chromeframe" target="_blank">the Chrome Frame plug-in</a>.
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2012 17:00:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Happy Wintereenmas!</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post13</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					Tonight is the last night of <a href="http://wintereenmas.com" target="_blank">Wintereenmas</a>, the video gamers' holiday.  To celebrate, we are releasing the beta of our latest game: <a href="http://inprod.co/games/imd" style="font-style:italic;">Inverse Missile Defense</a>.
				</p>
				<p>
					<img src="http://inprod.co/images/games/thumbs/imd_small.png" style="float:right; margin-left:16px;" alt="Inverse Missile Defense"/>
					<i>Inverse Missile Defense</i> is based on missile defense games, but played from the opposite perspective.  Instead of defending a planet from missiles raining down, you play as an alien ship trying to destroy the planet's inhabitants before they destroy you.  This game is being released as a beta, meaning we intend to add more features in the future.
				</p>
				<p>
					And finally, all of us at inProd would like to wish you a happy Wintereenmas!
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2011 22:10:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>New Year's Update</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post12</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					Happy new year!  We hope you all had a great Chanukah/Christmas/Festivus/Kwanzaa/[insert your holiday here] and new year's.  Today, inProd has some post-new year's presents to extend that fun time of year.
				</p>
				<p>
					<a href="http://inprod.co/public/images/news/2011/ltd_wave.png" target="_blank"><img src="http://inprod.co/public/images/news/2011/ltd_wave.png" style="float:right; margin-right:16px; width:128px; height:139px;" alt="Legit TD in Wave"/></a>
					First off, all our games have WaveThis buttons among the list of sharing options.  Until recently, clicking one would create a wave with a link to the game, but now we are taking advantage of the capabilities of <a href="http://wave.google.com" target="_blank">Google Wave</a> and actually <b>putting the game in the wave</b>.  Now you can share not just links to our games, but our games themselves with your friends on Google Wave.
					<br/>
					<small>(Note that a few games do not work as wave gadgets and therefore cannot be embedded in waves.)</small>
				</p>
				<p>
					Second, we have added comments to all of our games.  Now if you want to say something about one of our games, you can do it more easily than ever before.
				</p>
				<p>
					We have one other big annoncement that has unfortunately been delayed slightly.  It will hopefully be finished before the end of the month.
				</p>
				<p>
					We hope you will enjoy everything we announced today and look forward to bringing you more great productions in this new year.
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2011 19:45:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Now Share This!</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post11</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					As those of you who follow us on <a href="http://www.google.com/profiles/inprodgames#buzz">Google Buzz</a> or <a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Inverted-Productions/115574418462785">Facebook</a> have heard, we have made it easier to share games you liked with your friends.  Whenever you are playing a game, just scroll to the bottom of the page and click one of the buttons to quickly share it on sites like Facebook and Twitter.
				</p>
				<p>
					But that's not all that's new today!  If you take a look at the <a href="http://inprod.co/games">Productions</a> page, you can see we have redesigned it.  It now features screenshots and descriptions for games and is overall nicer to look at.
				</p>
				<p>
					One final thing to mention: This is the last update that will happen at <a href="http://inprod.webs.com">inprod.webs.com</a>.  That's right, we are finally moving to <a href="http://inprod.co">inprod.co</a>.  The Webs site will remain up for several months to allow those who have not done so to update their bookmarks and then it will eventually go offline.  As we said earlier, this is nothing against Webs.  We hope this change allows us to bring you even more great stuff in the relatively near future.
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2010 17:10:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Facebook and HTML5</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post10</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					It has been a little over a month since we started our buzz and it would appear that the buzz platform has not been as popular as we or Google expected.  So now we are launching another way for you to get inProd updates: Facebook.  Starting today we will post updates on <a href="">our Facebook page</a> just like we do on buzz.  And if you would like us to use another service as well (Twitter, perhaps?), just <a href="mailto:feedback%2Bsite@inprod.co">e-mail our webmaster</a>.
				</p>
					One more website update: you may have noticed that the link to the HTML5 version of our home page is back, and this time we have really taken advantage of all the features of HTML5 and CSS3.  You will notice that the page loads faster, looks crisper, and has some nice new features like animations.  If your browser supports HTML5 and CSS3, please give it a try and <a href="mailto:feedback%2Bsite@inprod.co">let us know what you think</a>.  Unfortunately HTML5 is still not completely supported in all browsers, but the new page should work in several major browsers including Google Chrome, Mozilla Firefox, Apple Safari, and Microsoft Internet Explorer with the Google Chrome Frame plug-in.
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 12:24:45 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>More stuff</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post09</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					Hi.  I know it has been a while since the last time the site was updated, but I can assure you we have still been working on new productions.  One is being released as a beta today.  It is currently called <i>The Fast Game</i> and is a tile-based box-pushing game with some interesting twists.  We still need to work on balencing the levels and adding a title screen, but feel free to <a href="http://inprod.co/games/fastgame">try it out</a> and send feedback.
				</p>
				<p>
					And speaking of feedback, you can now more easily send feedback.  On each production's page, there is a "Send feedback" link.  Just click it and you will be able to send e-mail to the people who worked on that game.  In addition, each person's name in the credits now links to his entry on the <a href="http://inprod.co/people">People</a> page, so you can directly contact the person who worked on the area you are giving feedback about.  Just remember to put a non-spammy subject line.
				</p>
				<p>
					And while on the subject of the <a href="http://inprod.co/people">People</a> page, you can see if you look at it that I <i>finally</i> updated it with the 2009-2010 inProd team.  But those are not the only updates to the site.  Changes have also been made to make text on pages more consistent and to optimize pages for search engines.  Hopefully this will help you to have a better idea of where you are in the site.
				</p>
				<p>
					Finally, an update on the state of our games.  I want to assure you that we ARE doing work.  That project we keep not telling you about is coming along nicely, as is another gome which is not incredibly new, but is still tons of fun.  We hope to have the game complete and the project in beta by this summer--no promises though.  Some members of the <i>Inverse Tower Defense</i> team have had some issues, but that game will hopefully be back on track soon.  And speaking of inverted games, <i>Inverse Cube Runner</i> has been updated.  In addition to some bug fixes it now takes up less space on the screen and has part of the debug mode made available for people who like things like that.
				</p>
				<p>
					So that is an update of what has been going on in inProd.  Oh, one more new thing.  Since writing these posts takes soooooo much effort, I will try posting shorter posts more often on the new <a href="http://www.google.com/profiles/inprodgames#buzz" target="_blank">inProd Buzz</a>.
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 21:20:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>New Game!</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post08</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					A <a href="http://inprod.co/games/icr">new game</a> has been added!  This is the first game in our "Inverted" series--games that "invert" the roles of the player and the computer in popular games.  This game is going to be in beta for a little bit longer while we iron out some more bugs.  The over time, we will also improve the AI and (hopefully) the graphics.
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 16:15:44 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>New Games And Small Site Change</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post07</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					If you go to the <a href="http://inprod.co/games">Productions</a> section of the website, you will see that there is now a table of our productions rather than the old list.  This allows you to quickly sort the items by type and status, rather than just by name.  That way if, for example, you have Java, but not Flash Player, you can sort the list to see which games are Java.  In addition, a new game, <a href="http://inprod.co/games/lagrange" style="font-style:italic;">Lagrange</a>, has been added.  This game was created by a friend of ours.  It puts a twist on normal shooters by not allowing you shoot directly at your opponent and instead forcing you to use the gravity of three planets of varying sizes to pull your shot to its target.  The game is still a work in progress, but feel free to give it a try.  A new version is in the works with better physics, a title screen, and the ability to start a new game from inside the game (right now you have to refresh the page).  Finally, we have announced a new game, <a href="http://inprod.co/games/itd" style="font-style:italic;">Inverse Tower Defense</a>.  This game is still very early in development, but we wanted to let you know that we are working on new games.  And on top of the, we have a really big project we are working on.  More about that later...
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 02 Oct 2009 22:15:54 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>HTML5</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post06</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					The next time you visit the Inverted Productions home page, you may notice a new link to the left that takes you to an HTML5 version of the page.  This is still experimental, and there is no major visible evidence of the change (except if your browser does not support HTML5 yet), but eventually this will be applied to the official site and will make it easier to add HTML5 features like video, audio, and vector graphics (graphics that stay sharp and do not pixelate when zoomed) without the need for plug-ins.  Note that this is currently only available for the home page, not all pages.
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 22:14:37 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>RSS Fixes</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post05</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					As you can see if you are viewing this on the news page, there are now buttons at the top of the page for quickly subscribing to the feed via iGoogle, Google Reader, My Yahoo!, myAOL, or Windows Live.  I might add more if needed.  Of course, you can also click the link on the line above those buttons in a browser like Firefox or Internet Explorer (7 or higher) that supports RSS to view the feed there.  In addition, I fixed the problem that used to cause errors when some RSS aggregators tried to read the feed.
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2009 22:04:20 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>New URL and BTS Improvements</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post04</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					Because John Renner, who was hosting the inProd website on his server, has left Inverted Productions, the site has been moved to <a href="http://inprod.webs.com">http://inprod.webs.com</a>.  Please check the new site to make sure there is nothing I forgot to upload to the URL (missing images, glitching code, etc.).  Except please ignore the glitching buttons on the inverted site.  I know about that and am trying to get it fixed.  Some behind-the-scenes changes have also been made.  These include replacing Dreamweaver's huge block of JavaScript with a simple three-line function I wrote myself and some minor changes to the CSS.  These changes will have no major effect on the appearence of the site and not mean much to non-geeks.  Finally, this will be the last update on the old site.  After this, it will stay in its current state until John decides to delete it from his server.
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2009 15:55:53 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>MORE Site Improvements</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post3</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					The navigation bar has been moved to the top and enlarged in response to feedback.  The buttons also now respond when you hover over them.  The old "low effort" demo of <a href="http://inprod.co/games/tpg"><i>The Two-Player Game</i></a> has been uplaoded and screenshot slideshows have been added on the <a href="http://inprod.co/games">Games</a> page.
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2009 16:26:44 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Site Improvements</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post2</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					The site has been updated with new navigation buttons and graphics.  I hope they will be to your liking.  If you have any suggestions, please contact me at <a href="mailto:feedback%2Bsite@inprod.co">feedback+site@inprod.co</a>.
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 19:15:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Welcome!</title>
			<link>http://inprod.co/news#post1</link>
			<description>
				<p>
					Welcome to the official site of Inverted Productions (bringing you great games since a month ago).  This is a prototype website, which I hope you will find to your liking.  If you have any questions, feel free to <a href="mailto:feedback@inprod.co">contact us</a>.
				</p>
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2009 11:45:00 EST</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
